Switching Goals is a family, tv movie film directed by David Steinberg.
Twin sisters Emma and Sam come up with a scheme to switch places
so each can play in the soccer team they prefer.
Emma Stanton, played by Mary-Kate Olsen.
Sam Stanton, played by Ashley Olsen.
Denise Stanton, played by Kathryn Greenwood.
Greg Jeffries, played by Trevor Blumas.
Dave, played by Joe Grifasi.
Jerry Stanton, played by Eric Lutes.
Switching Goals is a 1999 American sports comedy television film directed
by David Steinberg and starring Mary-Kate and Ashley Olsen.
The film premiered on December 12, 1999, on ABC as
part of The Wonderful World of Disney.
The Olsen twins play identical twins who are polar opposites.
The film explores themes of sports, football (soccer), twins, identity swap.